The Hamon has almost
reached my head and brain!
We must do something!
Move our move!
Lordeo, we'll get a new body for you.
Excerpt from the December 4th,
1888 edition of the London Press.
It has been reported that 73
of the 452 residents in the
town of Wind Knight's lot
have gone missing overnight.
The police have been pursuing lines of
inquiry based on certain witness accounts.
These accounts state that
four outsiders were seen
burning a man's clothing at
the base of a nearby cliff.
One of the four was
reportedly wielding a large
hammer and using it to
smash a curious stone mask.
Our work here is done.
Thank you
so
much for watching.
in the future...
I'll die! I'll go!
Heir to the Joestar fortune,
Jonathan Joestar weds Arena.
Only daughter of the Pendletons.
A couple will travel to the Americas.
Nice.
Blazes!
Look what time it is!
Their ship's about to leave!
Oi!
Mr. Speedwagon!
You almost missed being
able to say goodbye.
Sorry I'm so late.
So then, where are they?
They're both on board the ship.
It's about ready to sail.
What? It is?
Where are they?
I've got to see them!
Now then, Father Sticks, we expect to hear
great things from your mission to Mexico.
I'll certainly do what I can.
Jonathan Joestar!
Where are you?
Watch where you're going!
What makes this thing so
blasted heavy, anyway?
How should I know?
We've been hired by that Asian
bloke, so we move it where he says.
Boy, did you boys hear that?
Quit flapping your blasted cake hole.
Now move it.
We don't get paid till this job's done.
Ow!
Ruddy hooligans! Mr. Speedwagon? Hmm?
Look, they're up there. Hello?
Jonathan!
What a beautiful sight.
I wish you a long, love-filled life.
I'll always be here for you.
If you ever need me, just call.
I'll be there.
Though, at the moment, I'd
just be in the way, eh?
Bon voyage!
Have a wonderful trip!
Poor little bird all alone.
Did you lose your flop?
Iran.
Something wrong, love?
Dear, what are you crying about?
These tears that I'm crying are from joy.
Joy that I am here with you.
Even as a boy, you strove
to be a true gentleman,
a champion of others, no matter
the consequence to yourself.
And now that proud and noble
Jonathan Joestar is here in my arms.
And I have you.
When my heart was frozen in despair, you
warmed me and brought me back to life.
I am fortunate to have saved
a world that has you in it.
I only wish Father could have known you.
Iran, come.
Supper's waiting. Jonathan!
Um, I wanted to tell you to be careful
so you wouldn't bash your head.
I wish that today would last forever.
Damn!
It fell into the engine room.
That's a filthy place to go after it.
I could just sell it, but
it brings in the shackles.
Dear Lord.
You surely do seem to enjoy picking on me.
Oh, no.
I haven't the experience
drinking Amanda's.
Just a bit.
Barely enough to get the taste.
It really isn't strong at all.
I think it's good.
Here.
No, it can't be!
Jonathan?
Impossible!
There is no way!
He's here!
Dio's alive!
Arena, go!
Back to our cabin, now!
And don't forget to lock the door!
Hmph.
Eh?
Well, that's rather strange.
The lock's undone.
Queer bit of business.
I can see a metal catch
glinting on the inside there.
But that...
would mean...
That this trunk is locked from the inside!
Halt!
You can't escape!
Where is my body?
Dish!
Jonathan is so upset.
Something is wrong.
Jojo, do you see the condition
in which I find myself?
Your work.
There is a reason I display
myself to you like this.
Why would I show my weakness
to my deadliest foe?
Because though I once despised you,
now I have only the greatest respect.
For your spirit, your valor
in battle, your power.
I see it now.
How incredible you are, Tio. Jojo.
No.
If not for you, I would never have
obtained the power of the Stone Mask.
However, your damnable meddling
cost me world domination.
If there really is a god, one who
plucks the strings of our fate,
I am certain that our fates were
bound together for a reason.
Our two existences were only
ever intended to be but one.
And so I will take the body of
the only man on earth I respect.
Then I will live in eternal glory.
For that is the destiny
which is waiting for me.
There will be no pain.
That is the final gift I bequeath to you.
No, no, those eyes, I can't.
Live on as my body, Jojo.
Jonathan, what?
Freedom!
No! Jonathan!
Oh, a pity you wouldn't hear me?
If only you had remained
still as I told you!
Your death, in fact, would
have been quite painless.
Torn from your little
fairy tale into hell!
Thrust into a reality
you didn't know existed.
What will you do now?
Did Jojo never tell you of me?
The evil that dwells there in the darkness
I may not look like much right now,
but surely you remember me.
Iran Pendleton.
Wait, it's Iran Joestar
now, isn't it? Dio!
The ship's full of bonkers!
As you ordered, Lord, I drained
the life of only one passenger.
And now most of the ship has
joined our little family.
And now we will proceed to America.
Isn't that right, Lord Dio?
I can't speak.
I can't even take a breath.
I have to move.
Lorena.
Lorena!
I have to save.
Can't gather.
Hormone.
Well, how the mighty have fallen.
This sniveling whelp can't
even draw a proper breath now.
Now, he'll be causing no more
mischief with his Hormone.
This is what he gets for
crossing you, Lord Dio.
Now we are going to play.
Or maybe I'll just sit quietly and watch
while he suffocates slowly, ha ha ha.
Silence, Wang Chen.
There shall be no insult to Jojo.
He is the one man capable of
bringing me to the apex of my fate.
You will show him all
the respect which is due
to him by severing his
head in a painless manner.
Of course, Lord Dio.
The body of my dearest foe has
become my future! Jonathan!
He's up to something. Be careful!
He might have one last trick
up his muscle-bound sleeve.
Bah, he's done for.
Lord Dio overestimates his mighty power.
Well, Jonathan Joestar,
I'll scoop out what little brains
you have with my bare fingers.
Must save Arena.
I have to use the last bit of
hormone left in me all at once.
Please work.
Careful.
Wang Chen, look out!
something broke inside my body
something important what have you done
This is the end, the last Harmon I have.
Too weak to destroy that zombie
completely, but it was enough.
What?
What is he playing at?
Jojo has interfered with Wang Chen's body,
disrupting its functions without
bringing it to complete destruction.
He's made it seize tightly
onto a piece of machinery.
And the device it clings to so
immovably is the paddle's screw shaft.
The strength of a zombie is
sufficient to arrest the paddle.
If the shaft is stopped, steam pressure
in the piston will build up inexorably.
Under such conditions,
there is but one end.
The ship will explode!
Jonathan, what's happening?
Why is this happening to us?
You must leave, Iran.
Soon the ship will be destroyed.
I don't know how the things that
are occurring today are possible.
It's all too impossible to bear.
I don't know whether I
should cry or scream.
Perhaps I should just faint
dead away and block it out.
But there is one thing I know.
Iran Joestar will remain with her husband.
In the warmth of these lips I
feel the cool ebbing of his life
Jonathan Joe Star is dying But we
are together I want to stay like this
Until the ship explodes and everything
burns to ash until everything is gone?
It's alright if you cry,
but you have to stay alive and go on.
Just like in a storybook.
You want me to come to the aid of a
helpless child and escape to safety?
That's unfair!
Just sheer cruelty!
The only thing that I want is
to end my life here with you.
That woman died trying to
save her child until the last.
My own mother did the same thing for me.
Save yourself.
Take the baby. Hurry!
So your plan is to destroy
this vessel is it Jojo?
You never give up or give
in, no matter the odds!
But know this, determination
is not just in you.
I will live.
There is no one who can defy me.
I will take your body as my own.
Zombies hither!
Devour Wang Chen's body and
restart the piston. Once you have?
The end has begun.
It's already blown apart,
but there's still a way out.
I was protecting myself from
the sun's rays well before this.
Let it explode.
I already have everything
I need to survive.
Iran, take a good look.
Since Jojo can no longer use his ham on,
I'll remove his head and
take his body as my own.
Then I shall walk over and
lie down in my velvet boudoir.
That humble shelter is
marvelously constructed.
It could withstand a ton of dynamite.
Goodbye, Jojo.
And welcome to you, my new eternal body!
Jonathan!
Dio.
As you observed, it may be true
that our fate is to be together.
I feel an odd warmth for you.
For now, our lives are interwoven completely
and will end along with this ship.
Farewell to you, my beloved.
Jojo, let me go!
Release me!
Think of what we two can achieve!
You'd like a taste of
eternity, would you not?
I can heal your wounds.
You and Iran can live together forever!
Jojo!
No.
It's too late.
He's dead.
Jonathan Joestar passed away
into undeserved oblivion.
His life was an important part of
history, but invisible to ordinary people.
Most of humanity for whom he sacrificed
will never know of his
noble accomplishments,
but his descendants will.
The life within me, newly created by Jonathan
and I, will certainly hear his story.
Arena Joestar was soon rescued
afloat near the Canary Islands,
and the Book of the Stone
Mask was closed for a time.
But that was only the beginning
of a new, bizarre adventure.
I'll be the roundabout.
The words will make you out and out.
I spend the day your way.
Call it morning driving through
the sun and in and out the valley.
The music dance and sing.
They make the children really ring.
I spend the day your way.
Cold in morning driving through the sun.
And in and out the valley.
In and out around the lake.
Mountains come out of the sky.
And they'll stand there.
One mile over we'll be there.
And we'll see you.
22 summers, we'll be there.
We'll be there with you.
24 and 5, but we'll see.
I'll be there with you.
It was in the fall of 1938.
It's good to see you again, Speedbucket.
You bastard, how could you have possibly?
Have known where they were?
Teach him a lesson.
Joseph Joestar.
My friends call me JoJo.